I can't hold her much longer. She's taking on too much water.
我拉不住她了，她进太多水了
-What is going on back there? -Keep your pants on, Murphy.
- 后面怎么样？ - 管好你自己吧，马费
We blew the starboard engine. Port engine's way too hot.
右弦的发动机过热了
-Hold on. -Shorten the tow or cut her loose.
- 抓紧 - 把拖绳缩短或者割断
Epps...
爱普斯…
...get off my damn tugboat. We don't have much time.
…去那条船上，我们没有太多时间了
Move it, Epps. If she sinks, she 's taking us with her.
快点，爱普斯，如果她沉了， 会把我们也带下去
Got a punch in the port floater.
给我一个打孔机
-Five minutes before she floods. -Less than that!
- 在她沉前给我五分钟 - 没有那么久了
Get back here. We're cutting her loose.
回来，我们要切断绳索
-Cut her loose. -That' s it. Get back here.
- 切断绳子 - 是的，回来
Come on! You heard the man!
快点！你听到了！
T ook us three months to get her off the bottom. I will not lose her now!
我们花了三个月把她弄出海底， 我现在绝不放弃
Goddamn it, Epps! You can't fix everything!
见鬼，爱普斯！你没法修的！
Christ!
上帝！
-For the last time, get back here! -She's taking on too much water!
- 最后一次重复，回来！ - 她进太多水了
Why do you always have to break my balls? I said get back here!
为什么你总是不听我的？ 我说了回来！
Do you want me to come down there and kick your ass? Because I'll do it.
你想要我下去踢你的屁股吗？我会的
Here's to the best damn salvage crew in the business!
这里是最棒的商业搜捞队
-We did it, guys! -Yeah, look at that!
- 我们成功了，伙计们！ - 是啊，看看这些
All right. Nice work.
哦，好工作
-Here's to the fucking sea! -To the sea.
- 为大海干杯 - 为大海
To a job well done.
干的真漂亮
Mr. Murphy? I'm Jack Ferriman. I was wondering if I could buy you a drink.
马费先生吗？我是杰克.菲尔曼 我在想能否请你喝一杯
He doesn't drink.
他不喝酒
Could I talk to you alone?
我可以和你单独谈谈吗？
You talk to me, you talk to my crew. That's the way it is.
你和我谈的，都可以 和我的队员说，就是这样
I fly the Arctic Weather Patrol flights out of Mackenzie Bay.
我在北极圈气象巡逻队工作， 巡视Mackenzie海湾
Last month I was out in the middle of the Strait when I came across this.
上个月我在巡视的时候发现了这个
Congratulations. You found a boat.
祝贺你，你发现了一艘船
In the middle of the ocean, of all places.
在海的中间
I tried for radio contact and got nothing...
我试图用无线电和它联系， 但是一无所获…
...so I figured she had to be adrift.
…所以我想它是在漂流
In the Bering Strait?
在白令海峡？
That's miles from shipping lanes. Did you alert the Coast Guard?
那离航道几英里远， 你通知海岸警卫队了吗？
It's international waters, so they noted it and that's it.
那是公海，所以他们 记录了一下，就这样
You get a name?
你知道叫什么吗？
No, I put it out of my head until two days ago when I saw it again.
没有，我早忘了 直到两天前我又看到它
What are we talking about? What kind of tonnage?
你在说什么？它什么吨位？
Big. Huge. Could be military.
很大，可能是军用的
Let's say that we're a little bit interested.
那我们倒有点兴趣
What's in it for you?
你能得什么好处？
I want 20% finder's fee, whatever she's worth.
不管它值多少， 我分20％的发现费
-Have you told anyone else about this? -Not a living soul.
- 你还告诉过别人这事吗？ - 没有
-Give us a minute, will you? -Okay.
- 给我们一分钟，行吗？ - 好吧
So? What do you think, Murph?
那么？你怎么看，马费？
Who knows? Could be full of shit.
谁知道？可能它装满了狗屎
I do know one thing. I've seen strange things happen in the Strait.
我只知道一件事， 我在海峡见过些怪事
I know something else: Sea gives you an opportunity, take it.
我还知道：海洋给你 一个机会，你要抓住它
That's at least a week out of our way. We've been out for six months already.
去那至少要一星期， 我们刚在海上飘了六个月
I got a fiancee waiting, remember? I'm getting married in a month.
我还有未婚妻等着，记得吗？ 我还有一个月要结婚了
Plan was to go back to Anchorage. Starboard diesel needs an overhaul.
我的计划是回到安克雷奇， 右弦柴油机需要检修
-ln our business, the only plan is: -There is no plan.
- 在我们的生意里，唯一的计划就是： - 没有计划
If you don't want to go, that's fine. Let's tell him we'll get somebody else.
如果你们不想去，也没关系， 我就告诉他我们不去就行了
Wait a minute. Let's not be hasty. What's a ship like that worth?
等等，别急着决定， 这船看上去真的很值钱
Who knows?
谁知道？
Millions? Thousands? Could be nothing. Depends on a lot of things.
几百万？几千？ 也可能一文不值，很多可能
-Mainly, if we have the right to salvage. -Pretty big "if."
- 重要的是，如果我们去是对的 - 好一个如果
-What's the split? -We split it even, six ways.
- 意见不一致啊 - 就算我们的意见不一致，六种想法
-Even split? -Beats me paying you overtime.
- 不一致怎么办？ - 我会付你们加班费
I'm good.
我没问题
I'm in.
我干
Greer? What do you say?
格瑞，你怎么说？
All right.
好吧
Hey, Ferriman! Can you come over here?
嘿，菲尔曼！你能过来一下吗？
So this is the way it works. 1 0% instead of your 20% finder's fee.
这样吧，你分10％怎么样？
I can't let you take advantage of me like that.
我不能让你这样利用我
That's the way it is. Take it or leave it.
这只是个提议， 接受或者走人
Fine. But I go with you.
好吧，但是我要和你们一起去
Not on my boat, you don't.
别想，我船上不允许这样
Think I'd tell you where a fortune might be without insurance?
想想吧，我告诉了你在哪可能有 一笔没有上过保险的财富
There are five other boats that would jump at this.
有的是其他的船愿干这种事情
I come with you. So you take it or leave it.
我和你们一起去， 要么接受要么走人
Things are dull!
真惨！
She'll love it. What do you think?
她会喜欢的，你怎么想？
Too much off the sides, but I can come up with something she'll love.
太糟了，不过我可以 带些她喜欢的东西回去
-Shave that yourself. -Don't want to help me out?
- 你自己刮吧 - 不想帮帮我吗？
Who the fuck are you kidding? Everybody knows you Navy boys take it up the ass.
你开什么玩笑？每个人都知道 你们这些海军男孩都从屁股开始刮
-Enjoying the ride, Jack? -No, sir.
- 旅途愉快吗，杰克？ - 一点也不
Not the same as flying planes over ice sheets, is it?
和飞过冰原的感觉不同吧
-What's the appeal? -I could ask you the same thing.
- 为了什么？ - 我也可以这样问你
What's a nice girl doing in a dump like this instead of raising a family?
你是说为什么一个漂亮姑娘 爱干这种苦活而不去结婚生子呢？
I own a third of Murphy's operation. I'm not that nice.
很简单，我拥有马费三分之一的股份， 而且我没那么好
And these monkeys are my family.
这些猴子就是我的家人
Santos to Murphy. Come in.
桑托斯呼叫马费，完毕
-Yeah? -I think you should get up here.
- 是我 - 我想你该上来一下
-What is it? -I think you should see this!
- 怎么了？ - 我想你该看看这个
It was there a second ago! Ten miles to the northwest.
几秒钟前那有一个物体！ 在我们西北方10英里的地方
Would you turn off that fucking music?
你能吧那个变态音乐关掉吗？
I'm telling you, there must be a glitch. I saw it with my own eyes.
我说，那可能是干扰之类的， 我真的看到了
-Glitch, my ass. There's nothing there. -Give me a look at this.
- 干扰，这什么都没有 - 我看看
There it is! Right in front of you! Tell me you don't see nothing.
就在那，就在你前面！ 别告诉我你什么也没看见
Do you see what I'm saying? Do you see what I'm saying to you?
你看到我跟你说的东西了吗？
-Dodge, could you get on the bow light? -All right, Murph.
- 道奇，你能把探照灯打开吗？ - 好的，马费
-It's there, right? -There's something there.
- 它就在那，对吗？ - 有些东西在那
Hey, Murph, what's up?
嘿，马费，怎么了？
Vessel at position 7-5 north...
定位在北方7－5位置
...this is Arctic Warrior.
…这是北极战士号
Come in.
完毕
This is tugboat Arctic Warrior. Do you read me?
这是拖船，北极战士号， 你听到了吗？
This is Arctic Warrior.
这是北极战士号
Do you read me? Come in.
收到了吗？回答
Shit!
见鬼！
-Now do you believe me? -Holy shit!
- 现在你相信我了？ - 真见鬼！
An ocean liner? Where did that come from?
一条客轮？从哪来的？
It's the Antonia Graza.
安东尼亚·格瑞兹号
Jesus Christ.
上帝啊
This is civilian tugboat Arctic Warrior. Is there anyone aboard?
这是民用拖船北极战士号， 有人在船上吗？
This is Arctic Warrior. Can you read us?
这是北极战士号，能听到吗？
-You know her, Murphy? -Only in my dreams.
- 你知道她，马费？ - 只在我的梦里
Christ, she' s beautiful.
天那，她真美
Italian liners couldn' t compete for speed, so they built floating art palaces instead.
意大利的客轮在速度上没有竞争里， 所以他们就建了漂浮的艺术宫殿
She was reported missing May 21, 1 962, off the coast of Labrador.
她在离开拉布拉多港后， 于1962年5月21日被报失踪
Funny thing is, there was no distress signal. She just disappeared.
有意思的是，没有 求救信号，她就消失了
Ever since, every captain's been looking for her, hoping she hasn't gone down.
从那以后，每个船长都在寻找她， 希望她没有沉没
-Do you know what this means? -What?
- 你知道那意味着什么？ - 什么？
Under the law of the sea, she's ours. Let's not keep a lady waiting.
根据海洋法，她是我们的， 不能让一个女士久等
Santos, bring us alongside. Fire up the crane. We got business to do.
桑托斯，启动起重机，我们要开工了
When we get onboard, stay together. We don't know what kind of shape she's in.
当我们到了甲板，大家一起行动， 我们不知道这船的构造
-Take us up, Greer. -Aye, aye, captain.
- 把我们送上去，格瑞 - 好的，船长
Hey, Murphy, please remember to keep all channels open. Thank you.
嘿，马费，记得把所有的 通讯频道开着，谢谢
They won't let me go.
他们不准我去
Safety first. That's why you go last, Jack.
安全第一，所以你要最后上去，杰克
Can you sit down? I'm trying to keep this steady.
你能坐下吗？ 我正在试着稳住船
-I just want-- -Sit down! Get out of the way!
- 我只是想… - 坐下，别碍事！
Okay.
好吧
She's had some battering over the last 40 years, you can tell.
她在过去的四十年里有些损坏
Stand by. Setting you down topside.
站开一点，要到甲板了
She's still a beaut.
她仍然很美
Unbelievable.
真难以置信
You better stay alert. Watch your step.
你们最好保持警惕，小心脚下
40 years of rust can turn deck plates into quicksand.
四十年的锈蚀让甲板变得很危险
We'll make our way in at the fore, then check the bridge. This way. Careful.
我们排成一列走， 去检查一下船桥，这边，小心
-Forward mast is history. -Epps and Murphy, are they a couple?
- 前桅很有历史了 - 爱普斯和马费，他们是夫妻吗？
Hell, no. She's like a daughter to him. He'd be lost without her.
哦，不，她就像他的女儿， 他不能没有她
Superstructure's in decent shape. No sign of damage.
上层的建筑非常完好， 没有损坏的痕迹
-Lifeboats are gone, stern to bow. -Life preserver lockers are all empty.
- 救生艇没有了，船尾有点变形 - 救生箱都空了
Sure no survivors ever turned up, Murph?
确定没有生还者吗，马费？
Sure as we' re walking on the Graza, Dodge. This way.
就像我们现在在格瑞兹上 一样确定，这边走
Let' s go.
我们走
Jesus. She' s no fiddler' s green.
天哪，她甚至没长绿苔
You're wrong, Munder. She 's beautiful.
你错了，墨德，她很美
Whoever was on here originally sure left in a hurry.
那些原来在船上的人 一定离开的很匆忙
Murphy, come in.
马费，回答
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome aboard. I' m Julie.
女士们先生们， 欢迎登船，我是朱莉
I'll be your hostess this evening.
我是今晚的女主人
Have some respect, okay?
严肃一点，好吗？
Check out all those champagne bottles.
查查那些香槟酒瓶
Looks like we missed one hell of a party.
看上去我们错过了一次宴会
-And one hell of a hangover. -Shut up!
- 和一夜的宿醉 - 闭嘴
-Let's find the bridge.
- 我们去找船桥
-Such a manly man. -What?
- 真是个男子汉 - 什么？
-You all right? -Shut up!
- 你还好吗？ - 闭嘴！
Come on, Mary, let's go.
快点，玛丽，我们走
Murph, how many passengers did she carry?
马费，她当时载了多少乘客？
Over 600. The creme de la creme of society from all over Europe.
超过600，有欧洲各地的乘客
Crew of 500 from ltaly.
其中500个是意大利人
Talk to me. How's everything going?
现在怎么样了？
Okay, good. This companionway should get us to the bridge.
好了，这个升降扶梯能带我们去船桥
Here, Epps, hold this.
爱普斯，拿着这个
What's going on?
怎么了？
-After you. -No, after you.
- 在你后面 - 不，在你后面
No, no. After me.
不，不，跟着我
Tough guy.
坏家伙
Don't let go!
别让他掉下去！
-Pull! Pull! -Please, Epps!
- 拉住，拉住 - 爱普斯！
Please, Epps, don't let go!
摆脱，爱普斯，别让我掉下去
-Give me your hand. -Pull us up!
- 给我你的手 - 把我们拉上来
Oh, God!
哦，上帝！
I told you to watch your fucking step!
我告诉过你要注意脚下
-Oh, shit. Oh, Jesus. -From now on, you let me lead. Okay?
- 哦，见鬼，哦 - 从现在开始，跟着我走，好吗？
Let's go.
我们走
-I think I just shit my pants. -No, you always smell that way.
- 我想我尿裤子了 - 不，你总是那种味道
Compass is dead.
罗盘坏了
Helm's not responding, either.
舵也没反应了
Fuel tanks are empty. She must've rode on full throttle till she was bone-dry.
燃料箱也空了，她肯定是 全速行驶直到燃料用尽
Epps!
爱普斯！
I'm looking for the ship's log. Let's get this documentation back--
我找到船的航行日志了， 把它带回去吧
-Are you okay? -Yeah.
- 你还好吗？ - 是的
-You sure?
- 你肯定？
Let's get to it.
我们继续吧
Hey, check this out.
嘿，看看这个
-It's a watch. Congratulations, buddy. -No. Look again, you moron.
- 那是表，恭喜你，伙计 - 不，你再看看，你这傻瓜
It's a digital watch. Do the math. They didn't have digital watches in 1 962.
这是电子表，做做算数， 1962年的时候没有电子表
So we're not the first people to board this ship. But she's ours now.
那么说我们不是第一个 上这条船的人，但她现在是我们的了
Let's get some sleep, tow her at dawn. Let's hope there's no more surprises.
我们睡一觉，明早把她拖走， 希望不会有什么意外
Amen to that.
上帝保佑
Oh, God.
哦，天那
Epps, can I get some tea?
爱普斯，我能喝些茶吗？
Any sign of what might've happened? How she got here?
有什么会发生吗？ 她怎么到这的？
That's the $64 million question, isn't it?
那是个6千4百万的问题，不是吗？
Ever hear of a ship called the Marie Celeste?
听说过一条叫玛丽·西勒斯的船吗？
Twin-masted brigantine out of Charleston during the Civil War.
一艘南北战争时从查尔斯顿开出的双桅船
She was bound for London with a cargo of cotton.
她满载一船棉花驶往伦敦
Thanks.
谢谢
Two months after she set sail, she was sighted by fishermen off Tripoli.
她出航后两个月， 的黎波里的渔民发现了她
She was doing 1 2 knots an hour in a stiff breeze.
她在微风中以12节的速度前行
Something wasn't quite right. They didn't know what so they went onboard.
有些事情不对劲，他们不知道 是什么所以就上了船
You know what they found?
你知道他们发现了什么？
Nothing.
什么都没有
No passengers. No crew. No captain.
没有乘客，没有水手，没有船长
No sign of distress.
没有求救讯号
59 days after the last log entry, it had traveled 4500 miles across the ocean...
在最后的航海日志以后的59天里， 她在海上行驶了4500英里
...past the Rock of Gibraltar and into the Mediterranean Sea at full sail.
…穿过了直布罗陀海峡 的暗礁和地中海
And nobody at the helm.
却没有人掌舵
-What do you make of that? -A ghost ship.
- 你想说什么？ - 一艘幽灵船
Hey, you smell that? I smell bullshit.
嘿，你们闻到什么了吗？ 我闻到狗屎的味道
-Been on the sea a lot longer than you. -I know.
- 我在海上的日子比你多多了 - 我知道
Seen things that you can't even imagine.
看到很多你甚至想象不到的东西
Maritime history is full of Marie Celestes.
航海历史上有很多的玛丽·西勒斯
So, what's our plan?
那么，我们怎么办？
I think we should do what we came to do. Tie her up, tug her in.
我想我们该干我们该干的， 捆住她，拖回去
You think our little tug will pull this entire ocean liner?
你以为我们的小拖船 能拖走这么大一个客轮？
Not with the problems we got.
没有什么能难倒我们
We could set her at anchor and come back with two or three tugs.
我们可以让她抛锚在这， 然后回去叫两三艘拖船来
No, some Russian trawler will come along.
不行，俄罗斯的拖船会看到的
I've already looked for her anchors, anyway. They're gone.
我找过她的锚，不管怎么样，没有了
-What do you think? -Get the engines working...
- 你怎么想？ - 修好她的发动机…
...it could take us two weeks minimum to tow a vessel this size.
…要拖走这么大条船我们最少要花两个星期
For my share of what she's worth, I'd drag her back to Anchorage myself.
为了我的那份钱， 我会自己把她拖回安克雷奇
Don't let go!
别让我掉下去！
Help me! Don't let go!
救救我！别让我掉下去！
-Thought you might want a jacket. -Thanks.
- 我猜你大概需要件夹克 - 谢谢
Boy, do I miss that.
天那，我真想它
You okay? You seem quiet since you came back.
你还好吗？你从回来一直很沉默
I think I saw something I couldn't possibly have seen.
我觉得我看到一些我不该看到的东西
-Like what? -No, it's crazy.
- 是什么？ - 不，那太疯狂了
I'm curious. Tell me.
我很好奇，告诉我吧
I think I saw a little girl.
我想我看到一个小女孩
On....
在…
On the.... The boat?
在…船上？
Yeah. Looking right at me.
是的，就在那看着我
And then what happened?
那然后呢？
Nothing. She disappeared.
没有，她消失了
Sometimes, when I'd be flying for hours on end...
有时候，当我飞行几个小时以后…
...I'd think I'd see stuff too.
…我也会以为自己看见了些什么
It'd be there one second and gone the next. Like a dream.
它就出现一两秒钟然后就消失了， 就像一个梦
Thanks.
谢谢
-See you in the a.m. -Okay.
- 早上见 - 好的
Good night.
晚安
-See you tomorrow. -Yeah.
- 明天见 - 好的
She's got a big hole. She's sinking.
她有一个大洞，她正在下沉
-This is where the damage is. See? -Breach in the hull, about 1 0 by 20...
- 这就是那个破损处，看到了吗？ - 船体的裂口，大概十到二十…
-...torn to the port collision bulkhead. -Did it hit an iceberg?
- 左侧防撞墙被撕裂了 - 她撞上冰山了吗？
No, you don't need an iceberg to rupture a hull.
不，你不需要一个冰山去创造裂口
-She's been hit recently. -About a week ago, I'd say.
- 她最近刚刚被撞的 - 要我说，是大概一星期前的事
This is where we are.
这是我们所在的位置
The problem's this group of islands. Nothing spectacular...
问题是这组岛屿，没什么吸引人的…
...just rocks, a couple thousand seals.
…只有岩石，和很多的海豹
The Antonia Graza's caught here in this strong current loop...
安东尼亚·格瑞兹号 在这遇到强烈回流…
...and slowly she's been pushed towards those rocks. Last time she hit them.
…她被推向那些岩石，最后她撞到它们
-What about next time? -Won't be one.
- 然后呢？ - 不止一次
We've got three days to fix it. That's if the weather holds.
我们有三天的时间修好它， 如果天气允许的话
Why can't we tow it like it is?
为什么我们不能这样拖它走？
It'd be like towing a car with four flat tires.
那就像一辆车想拉动坦克
-It's a bump in the road. We can fix it. -Murph, bump in the road?
- 这只是块拦路石，我们能搞定 - 马费，拦路石
The breach we can probably patch if we can get to the inside.
我们能修补那些裂口 如果我们能进到船里面
We'll weld shut the flooded compartments, pump out the water up to the aft peak.
我们可以把破损的地 密封起来，把水抽干
On top of that, the rudder's jammed.
问题在于，舵坏了
We jerry-rig it, set a 38-degree current drift to clear the island chain.
我们大概检修一下，设定38度角的 航线，远离那些列岛
What does all that mean?
这些是什么意思？
I just-- That's a lot of work for three days.
我只是…就是说这三天 我们有很多事要做
But with the gear we've got onboard and what's on that ship, we can try.
但是这样我们就必须上船， 可是船上有什么，我们不知道
We can do it, right?
我们可以的，对吗？
With the gear we've got onboard, I can't fix our engine.
那样的话，我就不能修我们的发动机了
Quit bitching and overhaul the starboard engine.
你留在船上修发动机
-So that's the plan? -Just do it.
- 那就是计划？ - 照我说的做
-I'll call it in. -I wouldn't do that if I were you.
- 我要找人来 - 如果我是你我就不那么做
-Maritime law states-- -I know.
- 可是海员法… - 我知道
We just don't want any unexpected guests. Just leave it.
我们只是不希望有不速之客
Your call, captain.
你说的算，船长
All right, you know the drill. We do a complete recon.
好吧，你们知道程序， 我们先全面侦察一下这船
Make sure we've got no problems before we get to work.
确定我们开始工作前没有任何问题
-Stay with me, Greer. Don't wander. -Okay.
- 和我在一起，格瑞，别走丢了 - 好的
Dodge, Munder, go to the port collision bulkhead.
道奇，墨德，去防撞舱那
Jack and I'll work back from the fore. Call if you need anything.
杰克和我会回前面， 如果需要什么就叫我们
-How about a pizza? -You're so funny.
- 比萨怎么样？ - 你还真的很有意思
The only plan in this business is that there is no plan. What is that?
这种买卖唯一的计划就是没有计划，对吗？
What these people talking crazy for? That's not even good English.
这些家伙在胡说什么？ 他们的英语都还不流利呢
Hang in there, okay, preciosa?
挂在那，好吧， 宝贝?
Because someday he'll find some other genius to fix his boat.
因为他总有一天会找到一个修船的天才
You want to play like that?
你想那样对我？
It's still sweet, though.
但还好没什么大事
Light coming up.
打开灯
You were right. She is beautiful.
你对了，她是很漂亮
She sure is.
当然了
Epps, we're heading for the main engine room. Epps?
爱普斯，我们朝主引擎室进发，爱普斯？
All right, capitano.
好的，船上
Oh, shit.
噢，该死
We're gonna have to dive to get to that tear.
我们得潜下去修复受损处
Epps, the engine room is totally flooded.
爱普斯，主引擎室全是水.
Epps, can you hear me?
爱普斯，听见了吗？
Wait!
等等
What happened? You okay?
怎么啦？你没事吧？
What are you doing down there? Did you hurt yourself?
你在那干吗？没伤到自己吧？
What are you doing?
你在干吗？
The whole bottom's riddled with them.
底下全是无法解释的子弹
Looks like someone used it for target practice.
好像是有人拿来练习打靶
-That's the happy version. -What's the not-so-happy version?
-这是种快乐的幻觉. -那不是那么快乐的幻觉是什么？
There were people in there.
那儿有过人
I saw that little girl again.
我又看到了那个小女孩
What? Where?
什么？在哪？
-I must be losing my goddamn mind. -Well, did she say anything?
-我一定是糊涂了 -那她说了些什么？
Forget it. Come on.
算了吧，走吧
Murphy, come in.
墨菲，过来
Dodge! Anybody!
道奇！有人吗！
Shit.
该死
I think she's fucking with us.
我觉得她想耍我们
Looks like central laundry.
好像是洗衣中心
This vent connects to the forward hold. We need to see if it's flooded.
这个出口和前面的连在一起， 我们看看是不是也灌水了
-I may need help shutting it. -You sure we need to--?
-帮我关上它 -你确定需要--?
Murphy, where the hell are you?
墨菲，你在哪
-How long have they been here? -A month, maybe less.
-它们在这多久了？ -不知道，一个月或者更少
-What are we gonna do? -Get off this boat!
-怎么办？ -离开这条鬼船
-But the ship-- -lf it sinks, it sinks.
-但是这条船-- -说沉就沉，走吧
You're right.
你是对的
Stinks.
真臭
-What the hell? -We came through there.
-怎么回事? -我们从这进来的
No shit!
不会吧
Come on!
快
This way. Come on, Jack.
这边，快点，杰克
What the--?
什么啊--?
When'd you start wearing lipstick, Epps?
爱普斯什么时候开始用口红了？
Epps?
爱普斯？
" Francesca."
" 弗朗西丝卡."
Nice titties.
漂亮妹妹
Not that you can hold a candle to the future Mrs. Greer, though.
把握未来不是像握住蜡烛这么简单，伟人夫人
Come on, Jack. Stop dragging ass! What's your problem?
杰克，别捣鬼了，你怎么回事？
What's this?
这是什么？
Forget it. Let's go! Jack!
算了，快走，杰克
' 58 Jaguar X1 50. I've dreamt about this car since I was a kid.
58年产美洲虎X150， 我从小就梦想有一辆
We have to get out of here now. Do you understand? Now.
明白吗？我们现在要离开这里
There's something moving in there.
那有东西在动
Fuck!
操！
Oh, my God! I hate rats!
噢，上帝，我讨厌老鼠
What?
什么？
Oh, my God! Look at this!
哦，上帝！看这个！
I have to get Murphy.
我得去叫墨菲过来
Murphy!
墨菲！
Is someone trying to call me?
有人叫我吗？
Dodge! Munder!
道奇！墨菲！
Maureen....
莫林…
Who's Maureen?
谁是莫林？
It's my first name.
是我
-It's cold.... -He said "cold"?
- 这真冷… - 他说“冷”？
The galley.
厨房
-It's cold. -Please help us.
- 真冷啊 - 救救我们
Don't go in there.
别进去
You fucking assholes! Fuck you!
你这个混蛋！
Take it easy!
放松点！
You were fucking with us. We fucked with you. Why aren't you laughing?
你们作弄我们，我们就作弄你， 你们怎么不笑啊
Wanna hear something funnier? We found dead guys in the laundry room.
想听听有意思的事吗？ 在洗衣间里有尸体
And this in the cargo hold.
这是在货舱找到的
Need some help, skipper?
需要帮助吗，船长？
I'm sorry.
抱歉
-Jesus. -Oh, man.
- 上帝 - 哦，天那
Holy shit!
真见鬼！
Yeah!
耶！
We're rich!
我们发达了！
-You son of a bitch! -Rich!
- 你这婊子养的！ - 发了！
-Come on. Let's go. -Move this shit out!
- 快点，我们走 - 把这些弄出去！
One. Two. Three....
一，二，三…
How much you figure it's worth, boss?
你猜它们值多少，老板？
There's a lot of gold. Hard to know. Two, 300 million, maybe. Maybe more.
这么多金子，很难说， 大概有3亿，可能更多
-Jesus. -I don't know.
- 天啊 - 我不知道
Lock boxes with half of Fort Knox in them? They gotta be insured.
这样大箱的金子， 它们肯定都上了保险
No way somebody will let this much gold float away.
没有理由这么大笔钱 没人追查
Well, the markings have been filed down.
是啊，记号已经被弄掉了
-What does that mean? -Someone didn't want this traceable.
- 那说明什么？ - 某人不希望这笔钱被追踪
It's stolen.
这是被窃的
It may have to do with the reason this ship disappeared when it did.
这大概和这船失踪的原因有关
Wait. If the gold's got something to do with 1 962...
等等，如果这些金子 在1962年被偷的…
...what about the bodies? They can't be more than three weeks old.
…那些尸体呢？他们 不会超过三个星期
Somebody's gotta say it, and it might as well be me. This ship is fucked up.
也许我该说，这船太古怪了
Earlier I could swear I heard a woman singing. It's like she was....
早些时候我发誓我听到 一个女人的歌声，听上去就像…
-Like she was coming on to me. -Oh, no!
- 就像她就要走过来一样 - 哦，不
It was the sexiest voice I ever heard, man.
那可是我听过最性感的声音
-She got any backup singers? -Whatever you're on, get me some!
- 她还有后备歌手吗？ - 不管你有点什么，分我一份
Maybe you're not quite ready to get married, Greer.
或许你对结婚还没有 准备好，格瑞
-Fuck you. -Okay, guys.
- 去你的 - 好了，伙计们
-What about the Coast Guard? -No.
- 把这交给海岸警卫队怎么样？ - 不
You call the Coast Guard.... What if the gold did turn out to be stolen?
你叫海岸警卫队…你怎么知道 它们不会又被偷走？
Under maritime law, anything found in international waters...
根据海洋法，任何在 公海上发现的东西…
...belongs to the finder. Okay? That is the law.
都归发现者，那是法律
-Right. -Finders keepers.
- 对 - 发现人就是拥有者
If we're gonna do this, I say we do it now.
如果我们要这么做， 最好是现在
Get our boat going, grab the gold and get the hell out of here.
发动我们的船，拿走金子， 离开这个鬼地方
We leave the boat, take the gold. Who's with me?
我们带走金子，离开这船， 谁和我一起走？
I'm with the gold, man.
我和金子同在
Gold.
金子
-Epps? -I just want to get off this boat.
- 爱普斯？ - 我只想离开这船
Okay. Let's go to work.
好吧，开始行动
Okay. Warrior is in position, Murph. Can we please get the hell out of here?
战士们就战斗位置，墨菲， 我们能离开这了吗？
Yeah, preciosa! Smell that money! 1 00 million. You hear what I'm saying?
耶，太棒了，闻到了吗？ 一亿，你听到我说什么了吗？
1 00 million!
一亿！
Greer? Get those engines going.
格瑞？让这些东西转起来
I'm bringing the gold down.
我把金子带下来了
Yes, sir, captain, sir.
遵命，船长
Hey, Santos. Hurry your ass up, vato. We got to go like this.
嘿，桑托斯，快点干， 我们要走了
I wanna see these gauges rocking, because you just had an overhaul.
你们这些家伙快点动起来， 因为你们刚刚被我检修过
And you, I want you to give me some too.
而你，也给我点面子
Let's do this!
快点！
Hey, yo, Greer! Fire it up!
嘿，你，格瑞！ 启动它！
We're going to haul ass. Bring it on! We'll be so fucking rich!
我们要离开这， 我们马上就要富的流油了
Stop!
停下！
Stop! You don't know what you're doing!
住手！你们不知道你们在干什么！
We're good to go, skipper.
船发动了，船长
Don't start the boats! He'll--
别发动船！它…
Shit!
见鬼！
Greer!
格瑞！
Greer! What the hell just happened?
格瑞！怎么回事？
Jesus Christ! Fire on deck!
上帝呀！甲板着火了！
Santos! Greer! Munder!
桑托斯！格瑞！墨德！
I got you.
我抓住你了
-Epps! I got Munder! -Greer!
- 爱普斯！我找到墨德了！ - 格瑞
Come on!
快点！
Santos! Santos, answer me!
桑托斯！桑托斯，回答我！
I don't know what happened. The engine room just blew.
我不知道出了什么事， 发动机舱突然飞起来了
Maybe Santos rushed the engines, didn't seal up the gaskets right....
可能桑托斯匆忙检修机器， 没有垫好密封圈…
Jack, did you find anything out about this ship before you sent us out here?
杰克，你发现有什么东西 在我们出去前出去了
No, but l.... Look, we've got the gold, and we are still alive.
没有，但是我…你看，我们有 金子，我们都还活着
-Tell that to Santos, asshole! -Ease up!
- 你把这话对桑托斯说啊！ - 都别说了！
This is bullshit!
真见鬼！
Santos came here out of free will...
桑托斯也是自愿来这的…
-...just like us. -What does that mean?
- 就和我们一样 - 你说这什么意思？
-Enough! -Santos is dead because of you!
- 够了！ - 桑托斯因为你才死的
Come on! It's not gonna bring him back.
行了！那也不能把他带回来
Murph, it's not your fault. You know that.
马费，那不是你的错， 你知道的
How is he?
他怎么样了？
Here's the plan. We're professional salvors with a fortune onboard.
我有个计划，我们是专业的 打捞沉船财物的人员
I say we do what we do best: fix this rust bucket.
要我说我们就干点我们 最擅长的，修好这堆废铁
Control her drift. Clear those islands.
控制她的漂流，靠近那些岛屿
We can survive long enough to get picked up.
在被发现前我们可以维持很长一段时间
Why is this a question? We have the materials.
这有什么问题？我们有材料
Why don't we build a raft and leave? There is something wrong with this boat!
为什么我们不做个筏子离开这？ 这艘船太古怪了
-lf we stay here, we may not survive. -You want to build a raft?
- 如果我们留在这，就活不长了 - 你想造个筏子？
-I want to build a raft. -Even with the Warrior...
- 我想造个筏子 - 就算是战士…
...we were stretching to do this in three days. We can't do this.
…我们也得起码三天 才能修好，我们做不来
You're the best spot-welder I know.
你是最好的焊接工
We can do it right now, but I need you.
我们可以现在就干， 但是我们需要你
Fine. But there's no way we're doing a major patch-and-pump in the dark.
好吧，但是在黑暗里 我们没办法找到足够大的木板
Even with the lights we have, it'd be like going in blind.
就算是有光，我们也像瞎子一样
Okay, fine. We'll chill tonight and go in the a.m.
好吧，我们今晚休息，明天开始干
Greer? What do you say?
格瑞？你怎么想？
Now you want to know what the first mate has to say?
现在我能说什么呢？
I say go to hell, Epps. You're not qualified to get us off this ship.
要我说最好去下地狱，爱普斯， 你没资格领我们离开这船
Had Murphy let me do it my way, we wouldn't be in this.
要是马费听我的， 我们就不会困在这
-And the Coast Guard-- -So it's everybody else's fault, right?
- 至于海岸警卫队… - 这件事每个人都有错，对吗？
They'd be here and we'd be on our way home, millionaires.
他们会找到这，而我们 就会回家了，百万富翁
That's bullshit.
胡扯
Grow up, asshole.
成熟点，小鬼
Fucking bitch! Keep fucking talking. Say another word!
你他妈的！继续说啊， 再说一句试试看
Here it is. Katie. B-deck.
这个，凯蒂.B-deck
You were alone.
你是独自一人
1 00-to- 1, somebody poisoned the passengers to get the gold.
100比1，有人毒死了那些 想得到金子的人
Okay, Sherlock, if they were poisoned, why are these cans safe?
好吧，大侦探，如果他们是被 毒死的，为什么这些罐头是安全的？
They're still sealed. It's been sealed for 40 years. It's safe.
它们是密封的，它已经被密封 40年了，是安全的
Okay, shoot for it. Loser goes first.
好吧，猜拳，输者得先
-Paper beats rock. -Come on, man, best of three.
- 包袱胜石头 - 嘿，伙计，三局两胜
-Bullshit. You lost. -Where's your empathy?
- 胡扯，你输了 - 你的良心何在？
Winners do not empathize with losers. Bon appetit.
胜者不会同情输者
I screwed up.
我要振作
Damn! I knew better!
见鬼！我知道的！
I'll make it home to you, baby. I swear.
我会回家和你团聚的，宝贝，我发誓
What the hell are you looking at?
你他妈的在看什么？
-That's all right. -No way.
- 很不错 - 骗人
No, really. It's good. Look, I'm not kidding.
不，真的，真不错， 我没骗人
-Are you serious? -I'm serious. It's good!
- 你说真的？ - 真的，很好！
-You gotta try that! -That's good!
- 你必须试试！ - 很不错
That's great!
很不错嘛！
Katie?
凯蒂？
Can I tell you something else? We get back...
我能和你说点什么吗？ 我们回去以后…
...I'm gonna take my money and I'm gonna buy you a bathtub.
…我要拿着我那份钱， 然后给你买个浴缸
I'll get you a lifetime supply of titty magazines and toilet paper!
我会一生给你提供色情杂志和厕纸
I already beat you to it, bro!
我刚刚赢了你，兄弟！
There's something on your....
有东西在你…
Katie?
凯蒂？
Who, me?
谁，我？
Francesca, I know all of this isn't real.
弗朗西丝卡，我知道 这一切都不是真的
So I'm just gonna go with it, okay?
我只和你在一起，好吗？
Can't cheat on your fiancee with a dead girl, right?
不能和一个死掉的女人 一起欺骗自己的未婚妻，对吗？
Her parents.
她的父母
Please.
拜托
Don't close it.
别合上它
Haven't seen them for years.
很多年没见过他们了
They moved to New York.
他们搬去纽约
I was on my way to join them.
我要去见他们
But they're dead now.
但现在他们死了
-How would you know? -When you're like this...
- 你怎么知道？ - 当你像这样的时候…
...you know these things.
…你就知道了
My mother...
我妈妈…
...she made me this dress.
…她给我做的这些衣服
Do you like it?
你喜欢吗？
You remind me of her.
你让我想起了她
I don't think so.
我不这么想
Well, here. You should have this back.
这个，该还给你了·
Oh, God, you really are a fucking ghost.
哦，天那，你真的是鬼魂
Where are you going?
你去哪？
Santos was my goddamn responsibility.
桑托斯是因为我才死的
-The Lorelei. -She was adrift. We rescued her.
- 罗蕾莱 - 她漂浮着，我们去援救她
I've heard the story of the Lorelei.
我听说过罗蕾莱
I didn't know the Graza was involved.
我不知道
The gold was onboard the Lorelei?
金子是在罗蕾莱上的？
It says here " May 1 9, 1 962."
这写着“1962年，5月19日”
That's two days before your ship disappeared.
那是你的船失踪两天前
There were no survivors onboard the Lorelei.
在罗蕾莱上没有生还者
Jesus Christ!
上帝！
Where you going?
你去哪？
Most spirits are free to be with their families.
大部分灵魂去和他们的家人团聚了
So why aren't you with yours?
那你为什么没去？
-We're all trapped here. -Who?
- 我们都被困在这了 - 还有谁？
My shipmates and l.
我的水手和我
Even the ones who aren't marked.
甚至那些没有被标记的人
Marked?
有记号？
Katie, what do you mean?
凯蒂，你说的什么意思？
When the boat's full....
当船满了以后…
What? You can tell me.
怎么了？你可以告诉我
When he has all the souls he needs and has filled his quota...
当他得到了他所有需要的灵魂以后…
...we'll all be ferried...
…我们都上了船…
...to....
…为了…
What is it? What's wrong?
什么？怎么回事？
-What is it? -He doesn't want me talking to you.
- 什么东西？ - 他不想让我和你说话
-He who? -But I'm not like the others!
- 他是谁？ - 但我不像其他的人
You need to tell me.
你必须告诉我
You must go at once. Leave the ship while you still can!
你必须马上走， 在你还能离开的时候赶紧离开这船
Katie, what is it?
凯蒂，怎么了？
Katie! Katie?
凯蒂？凯蒂？
Epps?
爱普斯？
Come on!
快点！
We have to leave.
我们必须离开
Where you going, Murphy?
你去哪，马费？
What's the matter? It's me.
怎么了？是我
Santos.
桑托斯
It's no fun lying at the bottom of the ocean.
在海底躺着可不好玩
No lights at the end of the tunnel. Not for me, Murph.
无穷无尽的黑暗， 不该是我，马费
No 1 0,000 virgins at the pearly gates.
要1万名处女去天国
Because of the plan, I'm trapped on this dreamboat of yours.
因为这个计划，我在这条你的 梦幻之船上被捕获
So you know what? You're coming along for the ride.
你知道吗？你在继续这个计划
No!
不！
Murphy?
马费？
You all right, Murph?
你还好吧，马费？
You okay?
你还好吗？
-What's the matter, Murph? -It's me!
- 出什么事了，马费？ - 是我！
-Do it, come on. It'll make you feel good.
- 继续啊，快点，那样会让你好受点
Come on!
快点！
-Come on! -Hey!
- 快点！ - 嘿！
Oh, God. Epps, you okay?
哦，天哪，爱普斯，你还好吗？
-Keep him in the aquarium. -No, listen. He was drunk.
- 让他呆在这吧 - 不，听着，他只是喝醉了
He didn't know what he was doing.
他不知道他在干什么
Look, he just tried to kill you. He stays in there.
听着，他想杀了你， 他最好呆在这
Let's go find Greer.
我们去找格瑞吧
Any sign of him?
有他的消息吗？
No, we looked all over. Man's pissed off. Seems to happen on this boat.
没有，我们到处找过
-Least we weren't around 40 years ago. -The passengers were poisoned...
- 至少我们不在40年前 - 那些乘客是被毒死的…
-...to get to the gold? Isn't that--? -Extreme? Maybe, but if the shoe fits....
- …为了那些金子？ - 大概是吧…
Next thing you know, we'll be trying to kill each other.
你知道，也许下面， 就该我们自相残杀了
-What's with the heart? -Found it. Belonged to this little girl.
- 那是什么？ - 我找到的，属于一个小女孩
-What girl? -She told me to get off this boat.
- 什么女孩？ - 她告诉我离开这条船
-She's talking to you now? -What are you talking about?
- 她和你说话？ - 你们在说什么？
-You're seeing ghosts, Epps? -Just forget it.
- 你看到了鬼魂，爱普斯？ - 忘了它吧
So the ship's got a few kinks.
这船有些操作手册
Let's stick with Munder's specs and try to fix the ship.
我们照墨德说的做吧， 修好这船
No way five people and the gold will fit on any raft.
五个人加上那么多金子 不可能坐筏子走
Murphy's not going anywhere, and we're not leaving him here.
马费只是不知去哪了， 我们不能把他留在这
We stick with the plan. Fix the boat. Let's get going. Come on.
我们继续吧，修好船， 走吧，快点
That's the collision bulkhead hatch.
这是防撞舱壁
-Wheel's busted. It won't open. -Arming the C4.
- 齿轮坏了，打不开 - 装C4炸药
-Dodge? -I'm good.
- 道奇？ - 我很好
-Munder?
- 墨德？
Contact.
起爆
-There 's the tear, portside. -Looks bigger from here.
- 这是破洞 - 从这看上去很大
I'll shut her up, no problem.
我能把它封上，没问题
-Munder, rudder's fixed. You all right? -I'm good.
- 墨德，方向舵修好了，你怎么样？ - 我很好
- What do you think, Dodge? -She 'll hold.
- 你呢，道奇？ - 搞定
- We 're set with the pumps. -Start them up.
- 我们设好了水泵 - 开动
Copy that, Epps. One and two, kicking in.
知道了，爱普斯， 开动了
-I give it 1 2 hours till she's bone-dry. -Both on full.
- 差不多12个小时她的龙骨能露出来 - 都满了
Get ready, Epps. Here it comes.
准备，爱普斯，水过来了
Great work, guys.
干的好，伙计们
Damn. Current' s faster than I thought.
速度比我想的要快
If we control her drift, headed in this direction, we should clear those islands.
如果我们控制她的漂流， 朝这个方位，我们会看到岛屿
We'll keep it afloat until we get picked up.
我们会让它浮着，直到我们获救
Son of a bitch. We may just get out of this yet.
我们要离开这了
Kazillionaires.
太棒了
Check on the bridge when you're done here.
你们查查船桥
I'll see if I can find Greer down below.
我去下面看看能否找到格瑞
Greer?
格瑞？
Katie?
凯蒂？
Greer? Jesus!
格瑞？天那
-Shit. -Number two's clogged. Who's going?
- 见鬼 - 2号管堵塞，谁去？
You go.
你去
Shit. Every single time!
见鬼，每次都是我！
Oh, my God.
哦，天那
Come with me.
跟我来
I want to show you something.
我要带你看些东西
No!
不！
Come on! No!
快点！不！
Come on!
快点！
You can't die on me!
你不能死
Dodge. Murphy's dead.
道奇，马费死了
-What? -We have to get off this boat.
- 什么？ - 我们要离开这船
There's a reason you, me and Munder are still alive. That's why he came after us.
我知道为什么你，我和墨德还 活着的原因，那就是为什么他跟着我们
-To fix his ship. -I just saw Murphy. What's happening?
- 修好他的船 - 我刚看到马费了，出什么事了？
I don't know.
我不知道
I want you and Dodge on the rudder.
你和道奇去管方向舵
-But you just said-- -Listen to me.
- 但你刚才说… - 听我的
I'll get Munder, we'll see if the welds are holding. Stay here till we get back.
我等墨德，我们要看看焊接情况， 呆在这直到我们回来
I do not want you out of each other's sight. Take this.
我不想你们两个 超出对方的视线，拿着这个
Take it.
拿着
-Be careful down there. -I will.
- 在下面小心点 - 我会的
-That's it, then. We made it. -For now.
- 就是这了，我们搞定了 - 现在
-I'll check on Epps. -No, she said to wait here.
- 我去看看爱普斯 - 不行，她说等在这
-Yeah, but-- -Hey, she said to wait! So wait.
- 是的，但是… - 嘿，她说等，所以等！
You disgust me.
你真让我恶心
-What did you say? -You heard me.
- 你说什么？ - 你听着
You're a pathetic excuse for a man. She says, "Jump," and you jump.
你真是男人的悲哀， 她说“跳”，你就跳
You're disgusting. I don't have time for this.
你真让我恶心，我没时间和你玩
-Who the hell are you? -The question is, who are you?
- 你是谁？ - 问题是，你是谁？
You worship her, yet you've never had the balls to tell her...
你崇拜她，但你从没机会告诉她…
...because you're a weak, cowardly child.
因为你是个怯懦的小孩
However, if you'll kindly step out of my way, I'll make your dream a reality.
不管怎么样，如果你让开路， 我会让你好过些
You know, Dodge, if you kill somebody, you go to hell.
你知道，道奇，如果 你杀了人，你会下地狱
Well, you live for her. You willing to die for her?
好吧，你为她而活， 愿意为她而死吗？
I shot Ferriman. He's dead.
我杀了他，他死了
Yeah? Don't be so sure, Dodge.
是吗？别那么确定，道奇
-What are you doing? -Trip's over. I'm sinking the boat.
- 你在干什么？ - 游戏结束了，我要炸沉这船
-It's taken its last victim. -That'll kill us.
- 让它不再作恶 - 那会杀了我们的
-We'll have to take our chances. -What about the gold?
- 我们要自己争取机会 - 金子怎么办？
Fucking kidding? We're not getting the gold off this boat. Nobody ever does.
你开玩笑吗？我们带不走它们， 没有人能带走它们
Wait, wait. Wait!
等等，等等！
That gold can give us everything we ever wanted.
金子可以给我们一切想要的东西
We could have our own boat. The two of us.
我们可以有自己的船， 我们两个人的船
We could have a life together. You and me.
我们可以一起生活，你和我
What are you talking about? Dodge, we gotta get out of here. Now.
你在说什么？道奇， 我们现在要离开这，现在
Well, I can't let you do that.
不，我不能让你这么做
So that's it, huh?
就是这样，嗯？
All right. Okay.
好吧，好吧
You win. All right.
你赢了，好吧
Fucking bitch!
婊子！
All right, you win! Go ahead, do it!
好啊，你赢了，随便你，引爆啊
Go ahead. Blow it up!
继续，把它炸上天！
Kill us all!
把我们都杀了！
Hey, Dodge. Why haven't you asked me where Munder is?
嘿，道奇，为什么 你不问我墨德在哪？
Well, I suppose that's because...
哦，我想那是因为…
...I already know.
…我已经知道了
-You won't pull that trigger, Maureen. -Try me.
- 你不会按那个按钮，莫林 - 你试试看
Dodge made the same mistake. He's dead.
道奇犯了同样的错误，他死了
Katie told you, didn't she?
凯蒂告诉你的，不是吗？
Souls without sin can't be marked. Makes them tough to control.
没有罪过的灵魂不能被标记， 就无法严密的控制
But as long as I keep the boat afloat, we'll all go down together.
因为只要船浮着， 我们都会一起沉沦
-What the fuck are you? -I'm a salvager.
- 你是什么东西？ - 我是一个打捞人员
Just like you. You collect ships, I collect souls.
就像你一样，你收集船， 而我收集灵魂
And when I fill my quota, I send a boatload home.
当我集满了额度， 我送那船回家
This will make management happy. You see, it's a job.
那样老板会很高兴，你看，这是工作
Given to me after a lifetime of sin.
就会再给我生命
So if I lose this ship, management won't be happy, which is not a good thing.
所以如果我失去这条船，老板 不会高兴的，那可不是件好事
I'm not getting through to you. I'm asking for an exchange.
我不想杀你，我们做笔交易
This ship for your life.
这船换你的生命
I want my crew back.
我要我的伙伴回来
Sorry. Once a passenger's marked, they're mine.
对不起，一旦乘客被标记， 他们就是我的了
Then I guess it's over.
那么我想一切都结束了
All you had to do was fix the ship!
你所能做的就是修这船了！
I gave you a great opportunity.
我给你一个大好机会
All you had to do was take it.
这就是你应得的
What are you gonna do, shoot me?
你能怎么做呢，朝我开枪？
Careful. Hang in there, ma'am.
小心点，抓住，女士
No!
不！